hi everyone let's give us a moment just
大家好，让我们稍等一下
to set things up here
在这里设置东西
okay so welcome welcome so we are having
好吧，欢迎，欢迎，所以我们有
another Jakarta Tech Talk today we're
今天我们再来一次雅加达技术讲座
here with Emily Jiang and she's going to
和艾米丽·姜在这里，她要去
talk to us about micro profiles so the
与我们谈谈微观概况，因此
current status and and and and the
当前状态以及和和和
future of my micro profile so thanks
我的个人资料的未来，谢谢
Emily for being here and hopefully can
艾米莉（Emily）在这里，希望可以
someone give me a little note that you
有人给我一点笔记，你
can hear us and you see us and
可以听到我们，你看到我们，
everything is working as expected anyone
一切都按预期进行
in the chat you can you can send us a
在聊天中，您可以给我们发送邮件
quick message okay thank you sir
快速消息好，谢谢您，先生
so I think we're we're good to go so I
所以我想我们很好，所以我
will oh thanks Edwin I will now hand it
哦，谢谢埃德温，我现在把它交给
over to Emily and let her talk about
交给艾米丽，让她谈谈
micro profile Thank You Tanya let me
微型个人资料谢谢Tanya让我
share my screen yeah
分享我的萤幕
okay hopefully you can see my screen
好吧，希望你能看到我的屏幕
okay good morning good afternoon good
好的，早上好，下午好
evening I know we're on a globe and
晚上，我知道我们在地球仪上
thank you for coming
谢谢你的到来
I'm Emily Geum I'm a Java champion I
我是Emily Geum我是Java冠军
work for IBM and liberty architect for
为IBM和自由架构师工作
microphone and CDI so I spend most of my
麦克风和CDI，所以我花了大部分时间
time on open-source projects of
的开源项目时间
microphone open a boarding
麦克风打开登机
I'm also the thumping ideas are comes
我也是重击的想法来了
back elite so in this session I'm
精英，所以在本届会议上
beginning to talk about micro profiles
开始谈论微观轮廓
the current and the future so hopefully
现在和未来如此充满希望
as I know this talk you-you-you econo up
据我所知，你在说什么
up-to-date with what's going on in micro
最新的微事
profile and also told and we'll talk a
个人资料，并告诉我们，我们将谈论
little better how can you get involved
好一点，你怎么能参与其中
and etc on top a little bit about the
等最重要的一点
future and some of you may be wondering
未来，你们中有些人可能想知道
okay harmony why you are here to talk
好吧，和谐，为什么你在这里聊天
about micro profile this is a jacket on
关于微轮廓这是一件夹克
Tech Talk
技术讲座
actually macro profile is not poverty
实际上，宏观状况不是贫穷
cutter
切刀
however micro profile energy cottagey
但是微观轮廓能量平庸
they're complementary to each other
它们彼此互补
Dakara applause micro profile equals
达喀尔掌声微轮廓等于
amazingly powerful so when you think
非常强大，所以当你想
about cloud and evil micro services
关于云和邪恶的微服务
which is I think about 30 Carter EE we
我认为30卡特EE我们
should I think about micro profile so
我应该考虑微观特征吗
hopefully we'll find out was he in micro
希望我们会发现他在微
profile within the next an hour so is
一个小时之内
for the ones who do not know about micro
对于那些不了解微信的人
profile with as many couple minutes to
进行了多达几分钟的配置文件
have a quick intro micro profile is
快速介绍一下微观资料是
under eclipse foundation is an open
在日食基础上是开放的
source community originally it was set
源社区最初是设置的
up by IBM Red Hat Tommy to IRA LGC
IBM Red Hat Tommy创建的IRA LGC
and
和
some others individuals and soon the
其他一些人，很快
community growing very fast and now
社区发展非常迅速，现在
Oracle led been Microsoft so Java and
甲骨文领导微软，因此Java和
etc and kuru GE or joined so we are a
等和库鲁GE或加入，所以我们是
single community so when we work
单一社区，所以当我们工作时
together we do not differentiate ok you
在一起我们不区分你
are from areum you're from Red Hat
来自areum，来自Red Hat
we work together to evolve ourselves to
我们共同努力以发展自己
evolve the programming model for doing
改进编程模型
coordinated macro services to think
协调宏服务以进行思考
about how can we simplify the
关于我们如何简化
programming model to make Java
Java的编程模型
developers life a lot easier just focus
开发人员的生活要轻松得多，只需专注
on the business logic there is no
在业务逻辑上没有
reference the implementation which is
参考的实现是
different from a Java EE
与Java EE不同
so we because we do not want a
所以我们因为我们不想
differentiation the implementations all
区分所有实现
the implementations are equal we only
实现是平等的，我们只
publish API TCK and spans maven central
发布API TCK并跨越Maven Central
all in the github repository and we have
全部在github仓库中，我们有
a very frequent release we are
我们经常发布
lightweight and it's iterative very fast
轻巧且迭代速度非常快
so ism so far
到目前为止，
there's many macro profile rent homes
有很多宏观资料出租房屋
available for you like IBM has a
像IBM一样为您提供
WebSphere Liberty now also open Liberty
WebSphere Liberty现在也开放了Liberty
perhaps as newly released service model
也许作为新发布的服务模型
framework called Waka's I also have
我也有叫Waka的框架
small right and Sandhill pyara as a para
小右派和Sandhill pyara作为para
and Tommy tribe has 20 years a year and
汤米部落一年有20年，
Oracle has a helot and Mohammed project
甲骨文有一个默默无闻的项目
the owner is under Apache so so far we
到目前为止，所有者在Apache下
have like 8 as brand new specifications
有8个全新规格
together with 4 specifications we
连同4种规格，我们
directly borrowed from my javelin
直接从我的标枪借来的
so this is the kind of really sub
所以这是真正的子
pattern so since the October 2016 we
自2016年10月以来
have many releases so each year we have
有很多发行，所以每年我们都有
them sometimes three sometimes two etc
他们有时三个有时两个
we have a radius radius radius is a
我们有一个半径，半径半径是
macro provocateur to reduce the last
宏观挑衅者减少最后
last month February the it has the four
上个月2月有四个
horns opening a pi11 Opie fishing 103
角打开pi11 opie钓鱼103
and the rest climate 102 and in the next
其余的气候102和接下来的
like half an hour or 20 minutes also I
像半个小时还是二十分钟
will go through what's in the yeah in
会经历是的
details so is it as I have mentioned
细节就是我所说的
earlier the February DS is macro prefer
早些时候，2月DS是宏首选
to go to this is our AIDS platform
去这就是我们的艾滋病平台
release has that so far it has 21
到目前为止，它已发布21
component and release in means the
组件和释放意味着
individual releases they say you can see
他们说您可以看到的个人发行
yes like for specification CDR jax-rs
是的，如规格CDR jax-rs
JSONP antes in the derived a borrowed
派生的JSONP底注是借来的
from Java EE or you can post from
从Java EE或您可以从发布
Jakarta Guinea and then top with the
雅加达几内亚，然后顶上
Bruins or brand-new involved in micro
涉及微型的熊或全新
profile so in the next few slides goes
简介，因此在接下来的几张幻灯片中
through them what's in the photo or was
通过他们在照片中或曾经
he in the micro part to the out remedies
他在微观方面采取了补救措施
the first one in the photons to the oh
光子中的第一个到了哦
it has about three big
它有大约三大
functionalities included the first one
功能包括第一个
we introduced our config configuration
我们介绍了我们的配置配置
functionality which you can come Vega
Vega可以提供的功能
for tolerance interceptor priorities so
对于容差拦截器优先级，因此
that you can complete you can control an
你可以完成，你可以控制
interception invocation orders when you
截取调用命令时
when you have a customer written
当您有客户写信时
interceptors
拦截器
the second one is we want to go to react
第二个是我们要去反应
so we have a greater support for the
因此我们对
compression stage so if you use photons
压缩阶段，所以如果您使用光子
a synchronized
同步的
now you can retain a completion stage to
现在您可以保留完成阶段
utilize the Java eh completion stage of
利用Java eh的完成阶段
functionality to go to reactive the
去反应的功能
third one is we further clarify was the
第三个是我们进一步澄清的是
invocation order if you use multiple
如果使用多个调用顺序
photons the annotations such as if you
光子化注释，例如
use in this example use reach while
在此示例中使用
together with the timeout we will reach
连同超时，我们将达到
Y with the timeout apply to each wish
Y与超时适用于每个愿望
wise so basically we we clear is that
明智的是，我们基本上清楚的是
specify yes each root wise will have a
指定是，每个根智慧将有一个
timeout applied so this is kind of a
应用了超时，所以这有点
better example to demonstrate for
更好的例子来证明
tolerance with reactive programming
反应性编程的公差
patent so you can use the new jack size
专利，因此您可以使用新的插孔尺寸
2 to 1 that all our asked go to truly
2：1，我们所有的要求都去真正
reactive and then you can get the
反应性的，然后你就可以
completion stage and also this is all
完成阶段，这就是全部
unblocking and when you your completion
畅通无阻，何时完成
stage return with exception the reach
阶段回报率异常
while will be fired so basically what I
虽然基本上会被解雇
want to say you bear this in mind and
想说你记住这一点，
later on I will talk a little bit more
以后我会说更多
about reactive so the theme here is
关于反应式，所以这里的主题是
macro Foofa is green reactive the active
宏Foofa是绿色活性的
is the talking point for all the cloud
是所有云的话题
and native applications
和本机应用程序
so the second bigger feature is the rest
所以第二个更大的功能是其余
recliner 102
躺椅102
so the rezulin 102 introduced about 4
因此rezulin 102推出了约4
big functionalities the first one is the
大型功能第一个是
rest recline itself the Kriner API can
休息自己，Kriner API可以
support for tolerance annotations so you
支持公差注释，因此您
can annotate a reach while stuck in a
停留在
break on the photo on the rest reclined
靠在休息的照片上休息
interface
接口
on the top right hand corner it means
在右上角意味着
the resident client now can support
本地客户现在可以支持
connection timeout or read it timeout
连接超时或读取超时
the middle one is you can see now is
中间一个是，您现在可以看到的是
that we register Resta client you can
我们可以注册Resta客户
specify the base URI previously the line
在行之前指定基本URI
with red underneath it doesn't exist so
下方带有红色，因此不存在
you have to specify a config to be able
您必须指定一个配置才能
to configure now is much better for the
现在进行配置对于
developers interrogative specifies a
开发人员疑问指定
back-end URL and then during production
后端网址，然后在生产期间
this can be a usually overwritten the
这通常可以被覆盖
bottom base means now restaurant can
底层意味着现在餐厅可以
propagate the headers like her the
像她一样传播标题
residue on the previous it cannot
前一个残基不能
propagate to the HTTP headers so that
传播到HTTP标头，以便
some makes the using in like a in the
有些使使用像在
service mash for example e still
服务混搭例如e仍然
circumstances is very very comfy
情况很舒服
I mean very cubism because you have to
我的意思是非常立体主义，因为您必须
it's explicitly said as a header header
它被明确表示为标头
plan for the headers you want to
规划您想要的标题
propagate it now is rest recline I want
现在传播它是我想要的休息
to and we do that automatically for you
到，我们会自动为您完成
in the next few slides I will have
在接下来的几张幻灯片中，我将
quickly demonstrate and show you I mean
快速示范并向您展示我的意思
ok cool the snippet so the first one is
好的，很酷的代码段，所以第一个是
you can specify the default base URI so
您可以指定默认的基本URI，因此
you here you know so you you are calling
你在这里你知道所以你在打电话
the back end is 19 and 18 my base URI is
后端是19和18，我的基本URI是
the second of one means we register the
第二个是我们注册
resident lines that you can use reach
您可以使用的常驻线路
why and get a reach why on this
为什么，为什么能做到这一点
operation
运作
reach why we should reach why is a
达到为什么我们应该达到为什么是一个
foreign sanitation is the third
外国卫生是第三
the header propagation so you can't even
标头传播，因此您甚至无法
define the proper headers with the
用定义合适的标题
headers you want and then you can SE
您想要的标题，然后您可以SE
registra client headers and it is what
registra客户头，这是什么
we'll call these lines automatically
我们将自动调用这些行
propagate all these headers define the
传播所有这些标头定义
year so this is the what I mentioned
今年，这就是我提到的
earlier about time out so you can
大约早一点超时，这样您就可以
specify connection timeout and this is a
指定连接超时，这是一个
five second and you turn out so how long
五秒钟，你竟这么久
you want to wait for that for the result
您想要等待结果
and etc and then if you use the CDI this
等等，然后如果您使用CDI，
is the first one the programmatic way to
是第一个以编程方式
create a restaurant builder and the the
创建一个餐厅建筑商，然后
second align if you want to use that
如果要使用第二个对齐
other register as the client and also
其他注册为客户，也
you inject a restaurant you can use a
你注入餐厅，你可以使用
macro profile convict directly configure
宏配置文件有罪直接配置
the connector time out and read time out
连接器超时和读取超时
so that's a resident client the third
所以这是居民客户
why the open trees in 1.3 so the open
为什么在1.3中打开树木
freezing probably by if I you would
如果我愿意的话，可能会冻结
probably have guessed the open tracing
可能已经猜到了公开跟踪
103 is purely released because the rest
103被纯粹释放，因为其余
kind of 102 so open freezing previously
以前有102种冻
does not I mean welcome is there Jack
我不是说杰克在欢迎你
sighs Reza client basically is the
Reza客户感​​叹的基本上是
previously if you invoke like I you you
以前，如果你像我一样调用你
the client and invoke just as Reza
客户端并像Re​​za一样调用
client and then the rest clan you okay
客户，然后剩下的氏族你还好
now the background you will give you
现在您将给您的背景
look at our trees we have a two traces
看我们的树木，我们有两条痕迹
and twistz bandz there's no correlation
和twistz bandz没有关联
there and now open to using Windows
在那里，现在可以使用Windows
three automatic propagate ahead or
三个自动传播或
basically ISM the
基本上是ISM
the span a parent ID they are the same
跨度相同的父ID
so so that's where you can correlate
所以这就是你可以关联的地方
some suspense so that way
这样有些悬念
this is why you you have a one trace two
这就是为什么你只有一个痕迹两个
spans easy looks greater two tracks your
跨越轻松看起来更大的两条轨道
service invocation considering is this
服务调用考虑的是这个
these surveys coded system services
这些调查编码系统服务
service going to another service
服务去另一个服务
Marty easier to look at I mean where the
马蒂更容易看我的意思是
problem is if there's a congestion and
问题是是否有交通拥堵，
etc because the older bands connected
等，因为较旧的乐队连接
together and then you can even work out
在一起，然后你甚至可以锻炼
a wheesh elongation I mean takes the
我的意思是说
most time total fourth feature is open
大多数时间总的第四个功能处于打开状态
API 101 oh my dear I wonder why is that
API 101哦，亲爱的我不知道为什么
my men are update so is the the first
我的男人是最新的，所以第一个
ones that can generate some API was our
可以生成一些API的是我们的
patch method and also is a rest crying
打补丁的方法，也是在哭
interface group is previous is no
接口组是以前的否
escapes
逃脱
no it's escapes for API generation
不，它是API生成的转义符
Twista and also together with some other
Twista以及其他一些
or OS a factory reserva is no
或OS是否为工厂保留
appropriate Pio artifact message one
适当的Pio神器消息之一
so you matter wondering okay is micro
所以你想知道好吗微
profile to dota 2 was released in
Dota 2的个人资料发布于
February probably the normally would
2月可能正常
take a long time for the implementation
花费很长时间来实施
to catch up if you are like anyways Java
反正Java赶上了
he normally take a years ago years for
他通常需要一年前
the implementation to catch up probably
赶上实施
our eyes yeah our I will be will be on a
我们的眼睛是的，我们将在
magazine released however for other
杂志发行了其他
implementation to catch up in to take a
实施以赶上
take a long one your macro profile and
用一长串的宏配置文件
all of us working very actively and look
我们所有人都非常积极地工作，并期待
has is amazing I mean really is the
具有惊人的意思是
cadence here we have a macro profile 2.2
节奏这里我们有一个宏配置文件2.2
reduced only made February and now we
减少只使二月，现在我们
already go to open a bird in 1903
在1903年已经去开鸟了
implementation micro prefer to torture
实施微偏爱酷刑
for you to try and also sound hero 2.4
供您尝试，还可以播放英雄2.4
as the implementation as well on both of
以及两者的实现
them and support Java 11 so you can go
它们并支持Java 11，因此您可以
ahead to try it out now what I have
提前尝试一下，现在我有什么
described in the previous it feels right
前面描述的感觉不错
and plus some other like
还有其他一些
a futurist you are interested under
您感兴趣的未来主义者
micro profile okay so it's a this is
微型个人资料好，所以这是
like a no the creature overview about
像没有生物概述
what has been released up to now
到目前为止已发布的内容
under a microscope without you afters
没有你的显微镜下
are like micro prefer to the 3ds we also
就像Micro更喜欢3ds，我们也
have a snack like a standalone ladies
像独立女士一样吃零食
basically is I mentioned earlier micro
基本上是我之前提到的微
particles reactive season zero one
粒子反应季节零一
specification leather play gyms will
规格皮革戏剧健身房将
offer from Redmond so is the reactive
雷德蒙德（Redmond）的报价，所以反应式
streams popular creatures I want to give
流我想给流行的生物
you a like pizza you know about her
你像一个披萨，你知道她
reactive stream operators if you think
反应式流运算符（如果您认为）
about RAM as a stream in Java array so
关于RAM作为Java数组中的流，所以
Jo you to the stream you know it's the
乔你到流，你知道这是
kind of people study using Java 8 Anna
种人使用Java 8 Anna学习
cetera so so it's a stream that off and
等等，所以这是一条流，
then you can peel the Apple or you can
那么你可以剥苹果或
filter them you can you can do the map
过滤他们就可以做地图
and fan out rate on is a stream
而扇出率是一个流
similarly however in the java.util
但是在java.util中类似
stream is not reactive stream is all
流不是反应流
blocking operations in the in micro
阻止微操作
profile reactive stream we have like a
轮廓反应流，我们就像
terror act like a mini what traveler you
恐怖行为就像一个迷你旅行者
to dos stream per se para is a reactive
dos流本身对反应是有反应的
so you can build up a stream seminar and
这样您就可以建立一个流媒体研讨会并
system the Java though you to the stream
通过流将Java系统化
you can operate on and then you can run
您可以进行操作，然后运行
to render stream and anytime you can
随时随地渲染流
build up it will give you you know who
建立它会给你你知道谁
uses a competition stage and then give
使用比赛阶段，然后给予
you a completion stage and then you can
完成阶段，然后您就可以
play with of your operations on top of
充分利用您的操作
it so this is them like if I put this
所以这就是他们，就像我把这个
comparison here is a very easy for you
比较这里对你来说很容易
if you know the stream already to
如果您知道流已经到
understand reactive streams basically it
基本上了解反应流
is this is channel reactive version of
这是频道的反应式版本吗
the Java zone you to dos tree
您要做的Java区域树
and as I mentioned earlier in February
正如我在二月初提到的
we did accrue people to the 3ds
我们确实使人们加入了3ds
what was this year's radius pattern was
今年的半径模式是什么
the future already skated and actually
未来已经溜走了，实际上
we also discussed in profit in it he is
我们还讨论了他的利益
a from now on I want to release three
从现在开始我要发布三个
times per year we want to release in
我们每年要发布的次数
February June and October
2月6月和10月
so our next videos will be Jim the next
所以我们的下一个视频将是下一个吉姆
and also we discussed the matter in
而且我们在
macro profile we are allow we allow
宏配置文件，我们允许，我们允许
backward incompatible changes with very
向后不兼容的更改非常
strong reasons with the the back of
背后的强烈理由
other compatibilities have to introduce
其他兼容性必须引入
because of very strong reasons so it so
因为非常有力的原因
we try to control no to introduce back
我们试图控制不介绍回来
order compatibilities as you wish
根据需要订购兼容性
however if you must
但是如果你必须
yes you are allowed to to introduce
是的，您可以介绍
backward compatible incompatible changes
向后兼容不兼容更改
so in during this year we plan to do a
所以在今年我们计划做一个
metre radius to incorporate some decor
米半径结合一些装饰
you come at about changes so some I will
你来讲述变化，所以我会
go through it in the next few slides to
在接下来的几张幻灯片中进行浏览
talk a little bit more about what coming
多说些什么
and for other aspects in progress some
在进行中的其他方面
of them we Mak make to June release some
我们麦到六月制作的其中一些
of them we make it to may be unique to
他们使我们可能是独特的
October means say there is another new
十月意味着有另一个新的
spec order reactive messaging now you
规格订单反应式消息传递现在您
can see why I said microparticles
可以看到我为什么说微粒
reactive so this is another
反应性的，所以这是另一个
specification so this one is a directly
规范，所以这是一个直接
build upon a reactive stream operators
基于反应式流运算符
so the basic a logical for this reactive
所以这个反应的基本逻辑
messaging is we want to introduce very
消息传递是我们要介绍的非常
simple to use annotations we want to
易于使用的注释，我们想要
introduce annotations to say
引入注释说
okay I'm the consumer I will say okay
好的，我是消费者，我会说好的
are the incoming so I'm a consumer of
是进来的，所以我是
this message from this tree if I if I
如果我从这棵树上发出此消息
want to publish message I will say at
想要发布消息，我将在
all Auto going I want publish to this
我要发布的所有自动行事
tree basically this is a abstraction
基本上这是一个树
layer over messaging providers such as
消息提供程序（例如
Akaka i'm to TDM to Piana cetera as you
阿卡卡（Akaka）和您一起前往TDM到Piana cetera
know Kafka is quite powerful however the
知道卡夫卡很强大，但是
APR spi since the candle is is a little
由于蜡烛有点APR SPI
bit don't want you to get used to them
有点不想让你习惯他们
so so that's why we come up with all
所以这就是为什么我们提出全部
these simplified annotations and
这些简化的注释和
hopefully different the implementation
希望实现有所不同
will choose their own favorite method to
会选择自己喜欢的方法来
provide asserted Kafka MTP or mgt deanna
提供断言的Kafka MTP或mgt deanna
cetera so this is a news bag
等，这是一个新闻袋
so what is face if you wanna get
所以，如果你想得到的是什么脸
involved please like yeah is a listening
请参与，就像是在听
towards the end so I will tell you how
快结束时，我会告诉你如何
to get some involved get involved the
让一些人参与
other the other news bag is called a
其他的另一个新闻袋叫做
contact propagation as I mentioned I
我提到的接触传播
mean constantly we are going reactive
意味着我们不断地变得被动
the first-level reactive is reactive
一级反应性是反应性的
programming so the reactive programming
编程，所以反应式编程
to put it simply is completion station
简单地说就是完成站
and set remote is writing when you talk
并在谈话时设置远程正在写
about a multi-threading get asteroid and
关于多线程的小行星和
cetera and then the second a problem
等，然后第二个问题
your interface is to keep the parent
您的界面是保留父母
contacts so that's why this account has
联系人，因此这是该帐户具有
the propagation was introduced to two
传播被介绍给两个
cookies how to propagate the contact or
Cookies如何传播联系人或
to propagate the for example security
传播例如安全性
contacts how to propagate a CDI contacts
联系人如何传播CDI联系人
so this is the other give you a quick
所以这是另一个给你一个快速
example here you can executor this is
您可以在此处执行的示例是
the macro profile
宏配置文件
executor and then you can directly get
执行器，然后您就可以直接得到
to the
到
thread from there and then you can
从那里线程，然后您就可以
guarantee to have the contacts that you
保证与您保持联系
wish to be propagated and propagating
希望被传播和传播
the other existing that's like a
其他现有的像
reactive messaging and also connects the
反应性消息传递，并连接
propagation in the brand new stack and
在全新的堆栈中传播，
then we also making progress with on the
然后我们在
existing some specifications such as a
现有的一些规范，例如
healthy chat when we talk about health
我们谈论健康时的健康聊天
check that you automatically think about
检查您是否自动思考
Burnett is you know in kubernetes you
Burnett是您在kubernetes中认识的吗
have a readiness and Lebanese check this
准备好了，黎巴嫩人检查一下
is exactly what the designed to work
正是设计的目的
with kubernetes infrastructure in
与Kubernetes基础架构在
kubernetes we have Lebanese and
kubernetes，我们有黎巴嫩人和
readiness
准备就绪
whyever currently in the health check we
为什么目前正在进行健康检查
only have one and the point is a Strad
只有一个，关键是斯特拉德
health which is attend or limited with
伴随或受限的健康
the used in granaries
粮仓中使用的
so that's this is why we came up with
所以这就是为什么我们想出了
some different feature called we want to
我们想要的一些不同的功能
split a health check into like a to
将健康检查分为
endpoint wine the Lebanese to use with
终点葡萄酒黎巴嫩人使用
Burnett his alumnus Lebanese chap the
伯纳特（Burnett）的黎巴嫩校友
other is the redness readiness to use
另一个是发红准备使用
with rock granite his readiness problem
与岩石花岗岩他的准备问题
the other tech engine a health check is
另一个技术引擎的健康检查是
we TeamViewer the pillow debate
我们TeamViewer的枕头大战
previously that are currently a pillow
以前是目前的枕头
who uses all come up so which is cold
谁用完所有东西，所以很冷
and in some other programming model most
在其他一些编程模型中
used the payload is called Staters so
用过的有效载荷被称为Staters，所以
this is why we want in your or come to
这就是为什么我们想要您的到来
status to to make sure the macro service
状态以确保宏服务
design using micro profile you can
您可以使用微轮廓进行设计
interact well with some other micro
与其他一些微机互动良好
services reading in different languages
用不同语言阅读的服务
for for example Muji is an assertion
例如无印良品就是一个断言
so the next existing specification
所以下一个现有规范
matrix is also making making some
矩阵也使一些
changes so magics is introduced on
变化，因此引入了魔术
backorder incompatible changes so the
延期交货不兼容的更改，因此
currents like the matrix the annotation
像矩阵一样的电流注解
content this is the counter can go up
内容是柜台可以涨
and down actually this is a candle very
其实这是一支蜡烛
confusing now is that now it's a change
现在令人困惑的是，这是一个改变
there is some in the matrix to account
矩阵中有一些要说明的
County the can we go up if you want to
县，如果你想我们可以去吗
go down you use a new contour in the
下去，你在使用新的轮廓
cage the other bigger change is nicer
笼子里另一个更大的变化更好
change is when you reuse a matrix name
更改是当您重复使用矩阵名称时
so so that way you make your permissions
这样您就可以进行权限管理
his graph looks better so you can reuse
他的图看起来更好，所以您可以重复使用
a name by use a different tab the other
通过使用其他选项卡来命名
spec is a macro profile comfy is also
spec是一个宏配置文件，也很舒适
making good a changes so we want some
做出改变，所以我们想要一些
improve as a way to do that to cope with
改善作为应对之道
the dynamic configure changes so we
动态配置发生变化，因此我们
introduce a common ancestor which is
介绍一个共同的祖先
kind of proxy to wrap around the value
一种包裹价值的代理
so you can do a configured or access but
因此您可以进行配置或访问
if you want to work out from my art or
如果你想从我的艺术中锻炼出来，或者
port which is integer and then you can
端口是整数，然后您可以
do a comma go to access and you can say
做一个逗号去访问，你可以说
cash for 60 minutes and then build up
兑现60分钟，然后积累
your config access similarly you can do
您的配置访问权限类似，您可以执行
up you can do a map to a port other than
您可以将地图映射到除
the cache for 16 minutes second so I'm
缓存每秒16分钟，所以我
sorry I'm mr. Dom is the kind of yukos
对不起，我是先生。 Dom是一种尤科斯人
there port conduct like heart disease
那里的港口行为像心脏病
the previous victim of a port conflict
港口冲突的前受害者
the second wise I try to say differently
第二个明智的尝试
it's a it someone another port convey a
这是另一个港口传达的一个人
why is it supposed to be read a host
为什么要读取主机
accounting at the other ones supposed to
在其他人应该会计
read a quote company so easy for you
阅读一家报价公司对您来说如此轻松
want for this a host turn a port you
要为此主机将端口转为
want to them go to the hand in your hand
希望他们牵手
how can you make sure they like added
您如何确保他们喜欢添加
changes in time and etc so you know your
时间等变化，所以你知道你的
URL is it's correct so you can do a
网址正确无误，因此您可以
create a snapshot you can do a config
创建一个快照，您可以进行配置
they'll create a snapshot and then a
他们会创建一个快照，然后
snapshot will be just a fixed value over
快照将只是一个固定值
the snapshot you can always do that host
您可以随时执行该主机的快照
accompli by the time you take a snapshot
拍摄快照时完成
connoisseurship
鉴赏
and then the other couple changes is
然后其他两个变化是
that you are allowed to inject and know
允许您注射并知道
into the country so the plasmid or
进入国家，所以质粒或
address you can say okay if it doesn't
地址，如果没有，您可以说可以
exist
存在
I'll inject and know into the
我将注入并知道
cosmetologist previously I mentioned the
美容师以前我提到过
dynamic convict so programmatically
程序化的动态定罪者
to our content or access created a
对我们的内容或访问创建了
common ancestor which is panel the proxy
共同祖先是代理面板
and then you can also use the injection
然后您也可以使用注射
you can just say okay the URL I want to
您可以说好我想要的网址
cache it was three millisecond and
缓存了三毫秒，
wherever here you routing you need to
无论您在哪里路由，都需要
give it a provider you wrap around a
给它一个提供商，您将其包装
prophecy because the senior I started
预言，因为我开始
who you are
你是谁
the big version but the value so that
大版本，但价值使
way you have to wrap Rhonda you have to
您必须包装Rhonda的方式
inject the provider here so that's the
在这里注入提供者，这就是
quick overview of them
他们的快速概述
I mean convey and the other the other
我的意思是传达，另一个
specification is micro provide service
规范是微服务
mesh so I brought this up is you need
网格，所以我提出了这个是你需要的
some service Nash specification we would
一些服务纳什规范，我们会
like to put a macro profile in the cloud
喜欢将宏配置文件放在云中
infrastructure so the macro profile is
基础架构，因此宏配置文件是
the cloud native programming although we
云原生编程，尽管我们
to make sure it is the best programming
确保它是最好的编程
model made for the cloud so that's wise
云计算模型，所以这是明智的
we are conscious how well my crew
我们意识到我的船员有多好
profile can work well with layer salmon
配置文件可以与鲑鱼层一起使用
for example in a service match kind of
例如在服务匹配中
work well with yeast - if you
与酵母配合使用-如果您
he still has a summer requirement come a
他还有夏天的要求
group profile help so this is why we
团体简介帮助，这就是为什么我们
have a decent specification we actively
有一个体面的规格，我们积极
work on this specification and to make
根据此规范进行工作并制定
sure is updated with a new macro profile
确定已使用新的宏配置文件更新
specifications for example here we
规格例如这里我们
demonstrate is macro profile programming
演示宏配置文件编程
model initiative and I figured out extra
示范倡议，我想出了更多
rest the client cannot propagate the
其余客户端无法传播
headers I mean in the downstream service
我在下游服务中指的标题
so that's why we we talked to rest crime
所以这就是为什么我们谈过休息犯罪的原因
talk to okay APR of increasing and then
谈论好的APR，然后增加
which is why both the specification was
这就是为什么两个规范都是
updated the purely because our service
更新纯粹是因为我们的服务
mesh architecture so we would like to
网状架构，所以我们想
build the best breed who any model for
建立任何模型的最佳犬种
service mash to take you to we want to
服务混搭带您去我们想
take care of your prouder native
照顾你骄傲的本地人
application from the minute you are
从您一刻开始申请
creating your application to the minute
随时创建您的应用程序
you you are in production so all the
你在生产中，所以
layers we we are like considering how to
我们喜欢考虑如何分层
make that your experience a lot similar
使您的体验非常相似
a lot easier so either in the next cell
容易得多，所以在下一个单元格中
like changing our service match we want
就像改变我们想要的服务匹配
to consume macro prefer to go to to see
消费宏更喜欢去看
whether our chain we put in in a
是否将我们的连锁店
restaurant and open tracing has a fixed
餐厅和开放式跟踪具有固定的
problem so that we can see the trees the
问题，以便我们可以看到树木
correlation or propagate is well and you
相关性或传播性很好，您
can see they used to yoga and you can
可以看到他们习惯了瑜伽，你可以
connect all the spans together with that
将所有跨度连接在一起
I think he Islam I have gone through a
我认为他伊斯兰教我经历了
quick a bird's eye view about
快速浏览一下
I mean what's going on for the
我的意思是这是怎么回事
functionality point of view up to now
到目前为止的功能观点
you I think you know okay um you have
你我想你知道吗
all the nice good days a year so we're
一年中所有美好的日子，所以我们
kind getting started how can I create a
善于入门如何创建一个
my macro surveys using micro profile
我使用微观资料进行的宏观调查
luckily we have a tool called a micro
幸运的是我们有一个叫做微型的工具
profile starter so micro profile starter
配置文件启动器，所以微型配置文件启动器
is that it's a great - I I would like to
是一个很棒的-II想
give a bigger credit to Rudy in Para and
在Para和Rudy中给予更大的赞誉
will contribute an initial version on
将贡献一个初始版本
this one he got in touch with me where I
他与我联系的那个地方
go with the last year the old K this is
去年跟老K一起去
the kind of project I have what do you
什么样的项目我有你
think I loved it and then on the very
认为我喜欢它，然后就
quickly involved him in a community and
迅速将他纳入社区，
then and then is the kind of criticism
然后又是一种批评
report and I also want to mention says
报告，我也想说说
her and come from Red Hat we we work
她，来自红帽，我们工作
together since beta last year we work a
自去年Beta版以来，我们共同致力于
weekly basis and also I want to thank
每周一次，我也要感谢
the the Ryan from Tommy Schwab as well
汤米·施瓦布（Tommy Schwab）的瑞安（Ryan）
and to do the design basically we all
并进行设计，基本上我们所有人
put effort together and one make sure
共同努力，确保
all these macro service creation journey
所有这些宏服务创建过程
a lot simpler and we created at my
简单得多，我们在
service and the you can directly build a
服务，您可以直接建立
true the wren time you want and again
真实的你想要的时间
getting started and with this I want to
开始，我想
give you a bigot a member of a group
给你一个团体的成员
vast utter regime well with the time so
与时俱进的巨大政权
this is started or macro privada dot IO
这是启动或宏privada点IO
here so I can choose a version currently
在这里，所以我可以选择当前的版本
is micro prefer to the one I know is the
微型比我知道的那个更
possessor has read the issue and no one
拥有者已阅读该问题，没有人
gets a micro prefer to go through here
有个微人物更喜欢穿过这里
and also is here is the next one we also
这也是下一个我们也是
want to get at eleven person here
想在这里结识十一个人
as well so is the stay tuned is this
敬请期待，这是
so if I choose the choose this one and
所以如果我选择选择这个
then you can see you can see you can
然后你可以看到你可以看到你可以
have you have a full run home to choose
你有完整的回家选择吗
from so you pick a all your your best
因此，您尽力而为
around home and go with it
在家里和它一起去
my favorites open ability but I can do
我最喜欢的开放能力，但我可以
it Donald Donald okay what directly
唐纳德·唐纳德好吧，直接
Donald it
唐纳德
so here here it is about to work so now
所以这里在这里要开始工作
so all the code has been generated with
所以所有的代码都已经生成了
ICD - I see all the code generator
ICD-我看到了所有代码生成器
they're like no Mimi control so it will
他们就像没有咪咪的控制，所以它将
download the ladies open Liberty 1903
下载女士开放自由1903
which is the readiest in his mom and
这是他妈妈中最准备的
then very soon it will give me a while
那很快就会给我一段时间
hey that's good now you have baby pocket
嘿，那很好，现在你有婴儿口袋了
because use a jar there right so I can't
因为在那里使用罐子，所以我不能
watch ever manager an old woman's body
看着经理老太太的身体
now if I go to that yeah you can see all
现在如果我去那是的，你可以看到所有
these are unemployed so as I told you
这些都是失业的，正如我告诉你的
earlier here the health check we have a
早些时候在这里进行健康检查
health check so I will check see here
健康检查，所以我会检查看看这里
current leads outcome
当前的线索结果
so hopefully health check out to those
所以希望健康检查那些
who after to the load to the health
谁来后负重健康
check to the area down in the here will
在这里将检查到该区域
become a state works and that and also
成为一个国家的作品，而且
you have well like we have time at one
你就像我们有时间在一起
point request it used to to do that and
点请求它曾经这样做
so basically when remonstrate all
所以基本上当所有
different metrics and etc and you can
不同的指标等，您可以
demonstrate the opening API so this is
演示开放的API，所以这是
the rocket build on swagger API you have
火箭基于您拥有的swagger API
knowing blogger will notice no this one
知道博主不会注意到这一个
so we have a description and also the
所以我们有一个描述，还有
schema and also the response with a
模式以及带有
guest and so this means I get get I get
客人，所以这意味着我得到我得到
and then this is the matter name you can
然后这就是你的名字
go back we've set up dr. s and point so
回去，我们已经成立了博士。并指出
it's just a hello world so this is just
这只是一个世界，所以这只是
like give you a bird's eye view of what
就像给你鸟瞰什么
is starter so basically you can directly
是入门产品，因此基本上您可以直接
users start her on an Creator when time
用户在有时间的时候在创建者上启动她
to co-own rental I'm traversing want on
共同出租我要遍历的租金
the you can take hi different
你可以打个招呼
specifications for your for your macro
您的宏的规格
service and go visit so earlier I just
服务和去拜访，所以我早
showed you the macro prefer to do one so
向您显示了宏更喜欢这样做
you know I mentioned earlier is the
你知道我前面提到的是
other multiple is a lot to rent homes
其他倍数要租房子
but some runtimes or different speed of
但是某些运行时或不同的速度
the implementation like a map group
像地图组一样的实现
profile 102 is a lot more to choose from
配置文件102还有很多可供选择
like an Oracle honeyton petit Tommy and
像甲骨文的蜜蒂小汤米和
all these implementations for you as
所有这些实现为您
well okay this is the this is the
好吧，这是这是
starter the next release is a machinist
下一个发行版是机械师
microprocessor $3 in targets for the
微处理器目标$ 3
June so the tentative a a day is the
6月是暂定的一天
fifth June
六月五号
it's a hopefully it can include the
希望它可以包括
matrix to the oil health check to the
石油健康检查矩阵
old etc it's a stay tuned
旧的等等，敬请期待
Emily yes question yeah yeah I can hear
艾米莉（Emily）是的问题，是的，我可以听到
considering that you're kind of you know
考虑到你很了解
not too far off from the demo there is a
离演示不太远，有一个
suggestion to if you can show the source
关于您是否可以显示源的建议
code generated by microphone starter oh
麦克风启动器生成的代码哦
yeah okay thank you
是的，谢谢
so this is a generator so this is a
所以这是一个发电机，所以这是一个
source code here so this is you see this
源代码在这里，所以这是你看到的
Joshua's resource and here is the inject
约书亚的资源，这是注射
injective or value which is a cop tip
形容词或值是警察提示
and this is a Jacke cells and the point
这是一个杰克细胞和重点
this is a cough medicine
这是止咳药
justice so I'm Zen so this is an object
正义，所以我是禅宗，所以这是一个对象
is based so this is the application path
基于，因此这是应用程序路径
one weight is an agitator integer this
一个权重是一个搅拌器整数
is a canal
是一条运河
/hello and demonstrated earlier - Jesus
/ hello并在较早前演示过-耶稣
jugs as resource as well and this is a
壶也是资源，这是一个
health check
健康检查
so health chakra mentioned earlier in a
所以前面提到的健康脉轮
moment we have a one in point slash
当我们有一个单点斜线
health and I made demo earlier so he has
健康，我更早做了演示，所以他有
implemented health check and then you
执行健康检查，然后您
can say is a simple name unbuild
可以说是一个简单的名字unbuild
obviously this is the wines just just a
显然，这只是葡萄酒
start point for you and when you really
起点，当你真正
want to do your health check you need to
想做健康检查
check ok it's my memory like they are
检查好吧，这是我的记忆
nearly running out so that kinda thing
快要用光了，有点
is this the kernel is my database in no
这是我的数据库内核吗
respawning so this is some this is kinda
重生，所以这是一些
logic you need to put a print and for
您需要打印的逻辑和
the matrix here and you can inject the
矩阵在这里，你可以注入
magic so this is directly from macro
魔术，所以这直接来自宏
profile so you can you can gather matrix
配置文件，以便您可以收集矩阵
the folder like Metro vision time you
像Metro vision这样的文件夹
can do a time yeah these are the other
可以做些时间，是的，其他的
ones that age so you can click to them
那个年龄的人，所以你可以点击他们
these methods as a
这些方法作为
different stickers the gauge and this is
不同的贴纸规格，这是
the photon so you can do the full back
光子，所以你可以做背部
and time out so when you invoke this
和超时，所以当您调用此
operation you say okay I allow 500
操作，您说可以，我允许500
millisecond
毫秒
if you cannot return within 500
如果您不能在500内返回
millisecond I consider is a failure you
我认为毫秒是失败的
can have for that so this is specify
可以为此而指定
which for Becky wonderful back to so
对于贝基来说，这很精彩
this method will automatically be code
此方法将自动为代码
and this one the GWT so this one
这个是GWT，所以这个
demonstrate actually inject the GWT that
演示实际注入的GWT
claim which is cannot are acting on the
不能执行的声明
GWT token we use the micro profile GWT
GWT令牌，我们使用微观档案GWT
age used together with the Java EE
与Java EE一起使用的年龄
securities or Rose was allowed so
证券或罗斯获准
basically it's the only allowed the Rose
基本上是玫瑰唯一允许的
or configured or not protected to invoke
或已配置或未受保护可以调用
this operation and then also you can
这个操作，然后你也可以
inject a GWT token to his back what he
向他的背部注入GWT令牌
in the token in itself as because the I
在令牌本身，因为我
choose open a beret and my rental and
选择开一个贝雷帽，我的租金和
you can see here because I choose my
你可以在这里看到，因为我选择了我的
group referred to though to the one so
小组虽然提到了一个
here's our X now in this s to the 1 so I
这是我们的X，现在是s到1，所以我
can easily take me through the actual I
可以轻松地带我了解我的实际情况
can use the Odin Britain new features in
可以使用Odin UK的新功能
the micro cultural to and yeah and also
微观文化是的，也是
these in my comic keys and stature okay
这些在我的漫画钥匙和身材好吗
that's now pre-cum overview all those
现在是所有这些内容的总结
generated code so you guys are ugly
生成的代码，所以你们很难看
import into your favorite hiding and and
导入您喜欢的隐藏和
to start some editing and putting in
开始一些编辑和放入
your business logically thanks Emily
您的业​​务从逻辑上感谢Emily
you're welcome
别客气
okay so the
好的，所以
the and nearly to the end which is very
和几乎到最后这是非常
important I hope I hope all of you if
重要的是，我希望我希望大家
you have not joined the macro profile
您尚未加入宏个人资料
Google Group please please click on his
Google网上论坛，请点击他的
join the micro prefer Google group to
加入微宠Google群组，
join in the discussion and asking
参加讨论并询问
questions contributor answers contribute
问题贡献者答案贡献
any thoughts and we here to some like
任何想法，我们在这里喜欢
Syria we we we cannot operate all in the
叙利亚我们我们不能在
open
打开
this is that like her tomorrow maybe I
就像她明天一样
wake up oh I wonder what how can we cope
醒来哦，我想知道我们该如何应对
with this I can easily support or
有了这个，我可以轻松地支持或
question somebody else okay yeah that's
问其他人好吧，那是
a true problem and Joe this is maybe
一个真正的问题，乔，这也许是
this isn't maybe you want a possible
这也许不是你想要一个可能
solution we can fix it basically we all
解决方案，我们基本上可以解决它
like talk in public and trying to like
喜欢在公开场合聊天并尝试喜欢
come up with the best solution for the
提出最佳解决方案
problem and you feel I mean your user of
问题，您觉得我的意思是您的用户
micro profile want her write a blog
微型个人资料要她写博客
about it please log on to macro profile
关于它，请登录到宏配置文件
and start a contribute so we will come
并开始捐款，所以我们会来
anybody to read blogs on the priests can
任何看过祭司博客的人都可以
imagine and shout in the Middle East
想像和在中东大喊
here and to say Oh directly can you can
在这里说直接哦可以
directly like creator issues in the
直接像
micro profile did hub is there I wanna
微型个人资料做过枢纽吗？
publish my blog and etc so you're more
发布我的博客等，使您更加
than welcome to contribute in the blogs
比欢迎在博客中贡献
so all the blogs are listed here if you
因此，如果您在此处列出了所有博客，
want a contributor into any project
想要任何项目的贡献者
directly click on a project and to find
直接单击一个项目并查找
the ones you want and get involved any
你想要和参与的人
quickly show you something so here is
迅速向您展示一些东西，所以这里是
our Metro profile is the top page if you
如果您是我们的“地铁”个人资料，则是首页
create a project you can see all the
创建一个项目，您可以看到所有
project you just have a quick look
项目，您只需快速浏览一下
all I want fancy micro profile comfy you
我想要的所有微型个人资料都能让您满意
can go there you can chat John Gator so
可以去那里，你可以和约翰·加托聊天
you can chat on Gator and then you can
您可以在Gator上聊天，然后就可以
see oh I wonder what Unicode okay that's
看到哦，我想知道Unicode可以吗
he's a better way to to trace with a
他是一种更好的追踪方式
click on here and directly go to github
单击此处，直接转到github
and then you also you can chat on Gator
然后你也可以在Gator上聊天
is there so many ways to get into the
有太多的方法可以进入
community and start a contribute the
社区并开始做出贡献
other thing I want also want to mention
我想说的另一件事
is if your customer if you are customer
是如果你的客户，如果你是客户
or micro profile you are you need for
或您需要的微资料
production we would love you to directly
生产，我们希望你直接
to play on a mini micro provide options
玩迷你微游戏提供选项
so far we have connect collected about
到目前为止，我们已经收集了有关
10 customers so far I know is there some
到目前为止，我知道有10位客户
bigger customers like a Penguin's just
像企鹅一样的大客户
and also some new transit company and
还有一些新的公交公司
cetera maybe they don't wish to share
等，也许他们不想分享
your name I think is that is we don't
你的名字，我想那是我们不
ask like a to share your contact details
像一个人一样分享您的联系方式
person you just play a website there
您只是在那里玩网站的人
that's a good enough or even if you are
就足够了，即使你是
a no consultant if you like Adam I know
没有顾问，如果你喜欢亚当，我知道
he use micro profile or it is again free
他使用了微型个人资料，或者又是免费的
freely sharing the details here I don't
在这里自由分享细节我不
think so in some so it's um basically
基本上是这样想的
what I want to say if what you want to
我想说什么，如果你想
get involved please join the mailing
参与，请加入邮件
list if you want to contribute and to
列出您是否想贡献和
some to some project
一些项目
you brought the projects and directly go
你带来了项目，直接去
go to the arcade hub and also chat on
前往街机中心并在上面聊天
dj tre also we have we have the micro
déjàêtre我们也有我们的微
profit a ninja burn all the meetings in
忍者赚钱烧掉所有会议
the in this calendar and we also have
在这个日历中，我们也有
bi-weekly micro profile agar together so
每周两次的微轮廓琼脂
we discussed how to evolve this
我们讨论了如何发展
community so it's a which is on Tuesday
社区，所以是星期二
so Islam please please getting involved
所以伊斯兰教请参与
I'll bring me to the final page here so
我会带我到这里的最后一页
final pages is the reasoning here about
最后几页是这里的理由
micro profile and also the star micro
微轮廓，还有微星
profile also I want to mention open
个人资料我也要提及公开
Liberty is implementational man at her
自由是她的执行者
profile I won't mention the open Liberty
个人资料我不会提及开放的自由
I outdoor guide if you want to get if
我户外向导如果你想得到
you want to learn micro profile but I
你想学习微观概况，但我
don't know where to start we have open
不知道从哪里开始我们已经开放
able to guide here you just insert micro
能够在这里指导您只需插入微型
trial MacIntyre you can see a lot of
试用MacIntyre，您可以看到很多
guys would come up to is that every
伙计们会想到的是
micro profile specification has been
微型配置文件规范已
developed the sofa is a guide for it big
开发沙发是它的指导
we even have with a history of guide I
我们甚至有指导我的历史
have talked her kubernetes guide and etc
谈到了她的kubernetes指南等
so for example here is teach you how to
所以例如这里教你如何
use a fault tolerance that for example
使用例如的容错
and is going to open tracing so with
并将要打开跟踪，因此
that that's all I have for this session
这就是我本次会议的全部
are there any other questions please
还有其他问题吗
were welcoming questions and says our
欢迎问题，并说我们
thanks
谢谢
helping out oh there is a advant anks
帮助哦，有一个优势
Emily so it was really really helpful so
艾米丽（Emily），所以真的很有帮助，所以
you will see all the comments afterwards
您之后将看到所有评论
Emily but I'm super happy that we're
艾米丽（Emily），但我为我们感到非常高兴
getting positive feedbacks great thank
得到积极的反馈非常感谢
you again for inviting me I'm very happy
再次邀请你我很高兴
to be here because I know I'm with all
来这里是因为我知道我与所有人在一起
the micro profile community all of us
我们所有人的微型个人资料社区
like a truly truly believe in open
就像一个真正相信开放的人
source and we want to come together to
来源，我们想聚在一起
evolve the best programming model for
为以下方面开发最佳的编程模型
Dean cloud and Native American services
院长云和美国原住民服务
ok so if no questions thank you so much
好的，如果没有问题，谢谢你
of course the live stream is recorded
当然会录制直播
and will be available off of the YouTube
并将在YouTube以外的地区提供
and we'll be in touch next month we have
我们下个月会保持联系
another schedule Tech Talk so we're
另一个安排技术讲座，所以我们
super excited to talk to you again
很高兴再次与您交谈
shortly question that service smash is
很快就质疑服务粉碎
going to be a spec yeah it's a very good
将是一个规格是的，这是一个很好的
question
题
service mashup basically we prototype we
服务mashup基本上我们是原型
are trying to experiment and try out all
正在尝试并尝试所有
the micro profile specifications
微型轮廓规格
underwrite the best practices in this
在此承保最佳做法
very immersed in the service matches
非常沉浸在服务比赛中
back once we have done is teenagers is
回到我们做的是青少年
it Ronnie we would like to publish
我们要发布罗尼
through the specification however now
现在通过规范
you can directly check it out and build
您可以直接检查并构建
like follow the instruction there and to
喜欢按照那里的指示去
use a macro providing a service match we
使用提供服务匹配的宏
have a detailed instruction so macro
有详细的说明，所以宏
profile - service as - mash and ego let
个人资料-服务为-mash and ego let
me demo it let me use a famil few
我演示它，让我用一些家庭
minutes
分钟
this is a hotel other spec and meaning
这是酒店的其他规格和意义
we just back so far we haven't fun I
我们到目前为止还没来得及娱乐
need to evolve any API and etc however
需要发展任何API等等
is all the Stags in here we are still
是这里所有的雄鹿
trying to work more and we have the
努力工作，我们有
service match the service a so we have a
服务与服务匹配，所以我们有一个
to micro services so you can try it out
微服务，所以您可以尝试一下
all the instruction and etc event right
所有指示等事件的权利
he knows your point this one's the based
他知道你的观点，这是根据
on you still running in your service
仍然在您的服务中运行
lunch instead second setup so we have
午餐，而不是第二个设置，所以我们有
two services you can just follow the
您可以按照以下两项服务
instruction here and when can guarantee
此处的说明以及何时可以保证
that one method poetry always to
那一种方法的诗总是
environment yeah so back to the story
环境是的，所以回到故事
and yes when we kind of finish off the
是的，当我们完成了
experiment we want to maybe publish to
我们可能要发布到的实验
the specification basically not merely
规范基本上不只是
in the best practices about how to use
关于如何使用的最佳实践
something you know how to use a macro
你知道如何使用宏的东西
providing the service match also I wrote
提供服务匹配我也写过
her blog and relatives newsletter from
她的博客和亲戚通讯来自
business here was our under Jacksonville
这是杰克逊维尔的生意
this is that you know these mines the
这是你知道这些地雷
colonel
上校
longer version detail the version about
较长的版本详细说明有关的版本
about like a micro profile we study
就像我们研究的微观概况一样
Smash TV you search I can profile on a
搜寻粉碎的电视，我可以在
nice table you will get get here either
漂亮的桌子，你会得到这里
getting Eclipse newsletter or get with
获取Eclipse新闻通讯或与
Jack Sandra they are identical because
杰克·桑德拉（Jack Sandra）是相同的，因为
it is one directing take from the
这是从
article published under Eclipse
Eclipse下发表的文章
newsletter
通讯
okay okay well this is great um thanks
好的，好的，这很好，谢谢
again Emily and thanks everyone for
再次艾米丽，谢谢大家
dialing in and we will talk again next
拨入电话，我们接下来再谈
one well Thank You Tonya thank you know
一个很好，谢谢托尼亚谢谢你知道
bye
再见